{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Beta pleated sheets are examples of protein's", "opta": "primary structure", "optb": "secondary structure", "optc": "tertiary structure", "optd": "quaternary structure", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "BRACl, an inherited form of breast cancer, regulates cell division by", "opta": "binding to a DNA sequence", "optb": "complexing with cyclins", "optc": "binding to the cell outer membrane", "optd": "binding to the protein RAD 51 which repairs DNA damage", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Metastasis involves", "opta": "ability of cells to dissolve cellular matrix", "optb": "metalloprotein levels", "optc": "decreased levels of proteins that regulate metalloproteins", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Signal sequences are part of a protein that", "opta": "signal folding of the protein", "optb": "signal the protein synthesis on the ribosomes is ended", "optc": "transport proteins to other sites within the cell", "optd": "refold proteins in prion-associated diseases", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Individuals with PKU disease are mentally retarded unless", "opta": "phenylalanine in the diet is restricted", "optb": "tyrosine in the diet is restricted", "optc": "homogentisic acid in the diet is restricted", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Marfan's syndrome is thought to be a mutation affecting", "opta": "hemoglobin synthesis", "optb": "collagen synthesis", "optc": "metabolism of homogentisic acid", "optd": "insufficient thyroid production", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Cyclins are proteins that", "opta": "regulate ability of cells to invade tissue", "optb": "regulate passage from one stage of cell division to another", "optc": "regulate apoptosis of damaged cells", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Over 50% of common cancers are associated with damage to a protein, p53. This protein", "opta": "is a cyclin", "optb": "is a tumor supressor", "optc": "is an oncogene", "optd": "regulates apoptosis", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Protein folding is", "opta": "automatic, mediated by the protein itself", "optb": "mediated by other proteins called chaperones", "optc": "mediated by the ribosomes", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Sickle cell disease is due to", "opta": "a mutation in the beta chain of Hb", "optb": "a mutation in the alpha chain of Hb", "optc": "infection with a parasite", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The four subunits of the hemoglobin (Hb) gene represent protein's", "opta": "primary structure", "optb": "secondary structure", "optc": "tertiary structure", "optd": "quaternary structure", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}